Guide to the George F. Kunz Papers 1862-1932 MS 358
New-York Historical Society
- de Lagerberg, J., 1918, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lambert, M.D., Samuel W. (Century Association), 1913 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lamprectit, Sterling P., 1921 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Langeloth, Mrs., 1924, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Langford, Charles W., 1931 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Larned, William Trowbridge, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lawrence, Alice W., undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lawrence, Richard W., 1915 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lawrence, William (Century Association), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Leach, Henry Goddard (The Forum; Church Club), 1924-1931 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Leary, Theresa, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lebour, Nona, 1915-1916 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lee, Ambrose, 1908 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lee, Ivy L., 1918, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Lee, Sidney (Trustees & Guardians of Shakespeare's Birthplace), 1916-1919 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Leet, George, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Leidy, Joseph, 1909, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Leigh, H.M. (Harper & Brothers), 1913 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Leppert, R.E. (Literary Digest), 1929 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Letchworth, William P., 1908-1910 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Levy, Emile, 1889-1907 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lewis, J. Volney (Rutgers College), 1913-1918 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lewisohn, Sam, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lilley, Robert (Johnson's Universal Cyclopedia; Century Co), 1889-1894 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lincoln, Charles (New York Times; The World), 1908-1915 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lindsay, H. (Century Co), 1913 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lindsay, Samuel M. (Columbia U., Academy of Political Science), 1921 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lippincott, J. Bertram, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Littauer, Kenneth (Collier's), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Little, H.A. (New York Times), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Little, Joseph D. (Maiden Lane Historical Society), 1924 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Livingston, Philip (Metropolitan Club of New York), 1921 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Linde, Curtis, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Locke, Bessie (National Kindergarten Association), 1921 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Logan, Charles Thomas (Palisadian), 1910 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Lloyd, Cyrus D., 1922 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Long, Constantine(?) Fairchild (C.B. Richard & Co), 1900 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Long, Ray (International Magazine Co), 1926 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Loomis, Seymour C., 1921 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lord, Chester S. (New York State Department of Education; The Sun), 1894, 1921-1925 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lorimer, George Horace (Saturday Evening Post), 1908 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lothrop, Stanley (Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation), 1920 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lowell, A. Lawrence (Harvard U), 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lowell, Augustus, 1893-1895 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lowell, S.A. (Pendleton Tribune), 1891 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lowry, Helen Bullitt, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lucas, F.A. (American Museum of Natural History), 1918, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lucas, Jannette May, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Luckhurst, Charlotte Taylor, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lull, Richard S. (Yale U, Peabody Museum), 1915 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lummis, Charles F. (Landmarks Club of California), 1918, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lunt, Carroll (China Digest), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Luther, Agnes Vinton, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lydenberg, H.M., 1916 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Lyons, Henry (Tuttle, Morehouse & Taylor), 1903, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Misc. L, 1899-1915 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Doubleday Page & Co; American Monthly Review of Reviews; Columbia U Library (in German); African World and Cape-Cairo Express.
- MacAdam, George, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- MacCracken, Henry M. (New York University), 1908 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- MacDonald, George, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Macfarlane, Anna M., 1892 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- MacGrath, Harold, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- MacNeil, H.A., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McClenahan, Howard (Princeton U), 1925-1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McClure, S.S. (McClure's magazine), 1921-1929 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McConnell, Francis J. (American Association for Old Age Security), 1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Typed appeal pamphlet for the Association
- McDonald, James G. (Foreign Policy Association), 1921 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McKay, George L. (Grolier Club), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McKnight, Edna C. (Netherlands-America Foundation), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McRoberts, Samuel (American Arbitration Association), 1928 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- McWatters, Marie Wilson (Mrs. Frank), 1930, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Macy, Valentine Everit, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Maillard, Maurice, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Mallon, George B. (The Sun), 1902 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Mallory, W.H. (The Churchman), 1903 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Manning, Mary Margaretta, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Manning, William T. (Diocese of New York; Trinity Parish), 1919-1931 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Mansfield, Howard, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Manville, T.F. (Roosevelt Memorial Association), 1919-1915 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Marble, James E., 1911 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Markham (Department of Mines, Brisbane), undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Markham, Edwin, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Marks, Marcus M. (New York Daylight Saving Committee), 1921 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Marshall, Edward, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Marshall, Horace R., 1909 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Martin, T. Commerford (Scientific and Industrial Information Bureau), 1920 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Martin, W.A. (Hispanic Society), 1908 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Mason, C.B. (Rockwood Hall Country Club), 1926, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Matthews, Brauder, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Mayer, Jasper J., 1921-1925 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Mead, Walter H., 1882 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Meloney, Marie M. (Mrs. William Brown) (The Delineator), 1922-1924 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  The letters make clear that Meloney was acting as a go-between for Madame Curie and George Kunz. Dr. Kunz sent Madame Curie a few small pieces of Kunzite and wanted a small piece of radium in return. Madame Curie could not send radium for the American Museum of Natural History.
- Menkel, W. (American Review of Reviews), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Menken, S. Stanwood (National Security League), 1927 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Merkel, Otto Julius, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Impressions of post-World War I Germany in 1919
- Merrill, F.J.H. (New York State Museum), 1898-1901 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Metcalfe, James S., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Invitation to dinner to honor John Drew's 50th anniversary of stage acting.
- Meyer, Fredrick Fischer (Union League), 1926 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Mezes (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Mickelson, Albert H., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Middleton, Merle, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miers, Henry A. (Oxford University Press), 1901 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Milbury, Arthur Wellesley (Industrial Christian Alliance), 1894, 1924, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miller, Benjamin L. (Lehigh U), 1918 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miller, C.R. (New York Times), 1916 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miller, Edgar G. (Grolier Club), 1892 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miller, Jacob W. (Hudson-Fulton Commission, Naval Parade Committee), 1909 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miller, Lewis, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  The documents are a biography of Lewis Miller (1829-1899) written by his daughter, Mary Miller Nichols.
- Miller, Marion Mills (Civic Congress), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Miller, Thomas, 1918-1819 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Includes a 1917 train schedule for the Putnam Division Main Line. Letters include inquiries about visiting Tilly Foster mine.
- Mitchell, E.P. (The Sun), 1916 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Mitchell, Henry S., 1909 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Miyaoka, T., 1924 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moffat, W.D. (The Mentor/Crowell Publishing), 1924-1925 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moffett, Cleveland, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Montgomery, James Mortimer (Sons of the Revolution), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moodey, Margaret W. (United States National Museum), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Alfred D. (Presbyterian Church of the Sea and Land), 1920-1921 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Ann Louise, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Charles (Library of Congress), 1918 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Clarence B., 1907 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Ernst .D., 1930-1931 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Isabel, 1907-1908 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Moore, Jacob B. (New-York Historical Society), 1884 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Moore, R.B., 1925 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Moorehead, Warren K. (The Indian: A History series), 1901, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- More, Paul E. (The Nation), 1910-1914 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Moreland, James (Georgetown College), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Morgan, Appleton, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Morris, Anna Wharton, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Morris, Benjamin Wistar (Union League), 1931 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Morris, Gertrude, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Morton, Joseph L. (Grolier Club), 1893-1904 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Moses, Alfred (Columbia U., Department of Mineralogy), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Frederick Muller & Co., Amsterdam, 1885 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Muller, K., 1889 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Munroe, Charles E., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Munsey, Frank A., 1919 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Murphy, Andrew E. (St. Louis Post-Dispatch), 1909 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Letter regarding discovery of diamond mine in Arkansas
- Murphy, Franklin, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Murphy, Jeanette R., 1921-1924 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Muschenheim, William C., 1908-1915 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Misc. M, 1915-1926 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Nason, Arthur Huntington (Authors Club), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nast, Conde, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nelson, George Francis (Cathedral of Saint John the Divine), 1911-1916 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nelson, Robert W., 1925 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Neumuller, Walter, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Newell, Edward T. (American Numismatic Society), 1921, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Newell, F.H., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Newell, W.W. (American Folklore Society), 1900 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nicholas, G.S., 1912 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nichols, S.Van B. (Grolier Club), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Nichols, William H., 1925 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Norris, Jr., Hower, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Northcliffe (The Times, London), 1908-1914 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Noyes, Alfred, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Noyes, F.K. (The Sun), 1909 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Noyes, W.A., 1927 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Enclosed with letter is poetry by Charles Noyes, son of W.A. Noyes.
- O'Brien, Morgan J. (St. Vincent's Hospital, Advisory Board), 1926 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Ochs, Adolph S. (New York Times), 1915-1932 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Ogden, R.(?) (New York Times), undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Olcott, Eben Erskine, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Olschki, Leo S., 1908 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  One letter in which Olschki acknowledges Kunz's recommendation of Gardner Teall as a correspondent for his magazine La Bibliofilia; notes that a similar rrecommendation had been received from Belle da Costa Greene. See also the folders of Teall correspondence from 1908 (1908) below for further references to this matter.
- Opdycke, L.E., 1905 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Oppenheimer, Ida (Jacob A. Riis Neighborhood Settlement), 1922 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Orne, Henry M., 1908 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Osborn, Henry Fairfield (American Museum of Natural History), 1913-1922, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Osborn, William Church, 1915-1930 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  N.Y. Society for the Relief of the Ruptured and Crippled; Economic Club of New York (regarding The Town Hall debt).
- Osborne, Duffield (Authors Club), 1912 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Letter to Kunz informing him of his election to the club, with carbon copy of Kunz's response.
- Osborne, Thomas Mott (National Committee on Prisons & Prison Labor), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Owen, Henry H. (France-America Society Executive Committee), 1923 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Owen, Paul Stevens (Mohegan Lake School/St. Mary's Church), 1930 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Page, Howard (Van Cortlandt House), 1910 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Page, Walter H. (The World's Work), 1909-1911 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Painter, H.M. (Grolier Club), 1911 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Palache, Charles (Harvard U, Mineralogical Lab), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Palmer, Bertha H. (World's Columbian Exposition, Board of Lady Managers), 1892-1893 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Paret, Thomas Dunkin (Grolier Club), 1903 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Paris, Francis(?), 1932 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Parish, Jr., Daniel (American Numismatic & Archaeological Society), 1894 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Parish, Edward C., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Parker, Arthur Caswell, 1904-1905 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Two letters from Parker in which he discusses his interest in establishing an industrial training school for Indians (specifically Iroquois) and the translation and archaeological work he is doing, thanks to Kunz's help. Two related letters from New York Governor B.B. Odell, Jr. to Kunz are included here. The set of documents also includes a small pamphlet advertising a lecture series "The Historic Iroquois Indians" by Parker (who is referred to in the pamphlet as Gah-wah-so-wah-neh, of the Seneca Nation Bear Clan).
- Parker, Katherine L., 1924-1925 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Parks, G. Elton, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Parsons, William Barclay, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Parsons, Jno. E. (Hudson-Fulton Tercentenary, Inwood Park Committee), 1908 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Paterson, A., 1903 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Patlsits, Victor H. (New York Public Library), 1921-1926 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Patten, Henry A. (Union League), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Patterson, Ernest Minor (American Academy of Political & Social Science), 1930 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Patterson, Howard (Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission), 1909 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Patton, C.A. (Aldine Club), 1896 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Payne, John Barton (American Red Cross), 1926 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Peabody, Charles J., 1923 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Peabody, George Foster, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Pegram, George B. (Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission), 1909 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Pell, Theodore Roosevelt, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Includes a Seventy-first birthday testimonial to John Stuart White, LLD., Head Master of the Berkeley School, NY.
- Penniman, Josiah H. (University of Pennsylvania), 1928 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  One letter from the University Provost to Clarence S. Bement expressing their enthusiasm at having his collection of minerals deposited there.
- Pepper, William, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Perkins, George Walbridge, 1913-1919 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Perry, Edward Delaware (Century Association), 1928-1930 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Perry, Lucy W., 1903 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Perry, Raymond (Salmagundi Club), 1922 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Peter, Harry (Grolier Club), 1931 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Peters, John P. (Century Association), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Petit, Georges (Dr.) (Societe Contre l'Abus du Tabac), 1899 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  One letter, in French.
- Petrie, William Matthew Flinders, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Phillips, Nathaniel (League for American Citizenship), 1928 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Phipps, Annie, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pierce, John (John Skinner, dealer), 1895-1896 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pierson, B.W. (Grolier Club/Century Association), 1905 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pierson, Mary J., undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pitcher, Charlotte A., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pitt, Victor (Wide World magazine), 1914 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Planter, Louise E. (Joan of Arc Statue Committee), undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Plummer, John, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Poillon, William (American Numismatic and Archaeological Society), 1907-1908 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Polifeme, Carlo (Mme.) ("Le Lyceum" Société des Femmes de France à New York), 1915, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pollock, Channing, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pope, Virginia, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Porter, George D., undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Porter, Polly, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Porter, Robert R. (The Times, London), 1910 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Post, Regis H. (Metropolitan magazine), 1916 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Potter, Henry C., 1906 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Potter, Henry Noel, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Powell, Vrancia Chace (Mrs. George Townsend Powell), undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Poynton, John A. (Century Association), 1921 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pratt, Frederic B. (Century Association), 1908, 1917, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pratt, Helen Marshall, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Prentice, John H. (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Presley, Frank (Dinner in Honor of Dan Beard Committee), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Preston, Blanche Preston, 1920, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Preusser, R.F., circa 1906 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Manuscript of Preusser's poem "The Diamond" from his book "Brain Food for Old & Young."
- Price, Ira M. (University of Chicago), 1905 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pritchett, Erastus(?) Allister, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pritchett, Henry S. (Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching), 1920 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pritchett, Thomas James (Social Life magazine), undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Proctor, Thomas Redfield, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pryibil, Letitia P., 1918 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pulitzer, Ralph (The World), 1915 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Purington, C.W., 1917 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Putnam, G.H. (G.P. Putnam's Sons), 1907-1918 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Pyne, 2nd, Percy R., 1915 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Misc. P (Cooper Union), 1892 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Quackinbas, John D. (Columbia College), undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Quaritch, Bernard (bookseller), 1885-1903 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Quinby, Florence C., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Rand, C, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Raney, W.L. (American Library Association), 1919 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rasor, Paul E. (Union League), 1916 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rathom, John R., 1923 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Redfield, William C. (National Institute of Social Sciences), 1926 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Reed, Thomas P. (Royal Geographical Society of Australasia), 1912 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rees, J.K. (Columbia U., Astronomical Observatory), 1900-1901 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Reid, Sarah H., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Reinach, Salomon (Musee de St. Germain), 1910 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Remick, Carrie A., 1908 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Remsen, Ira (Johns Hopkins U), 1906-1908 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Reynolds, Cuyler (Albany Institute), 1909 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rhinelander, Philip, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rice, Calvin W., 1926 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Richardson, Lucy C., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Richmond, Lizzie D., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rickard, T.A., 1925 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ridder, Herman (New-Yorker Staats-Zeitung), 1906-1913 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Riggs, Arthur Stanley (Art and Archaeology Press), 1925-1928 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rines, George E. (Scientific American), 1903, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Riordan, D.M., 1918 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ritti, Paul, 1922-1930 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Two letters and a bulletin, all in French.
- Robbins, Emily (Committee of One Hundred on National Health), 1912 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Robbins, Howard C. (Cathedral of St. John the Divine), 1919 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Robins, Thomas, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Roderick, Stella Virginia (Everybody's Magazine), 1912 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rogers, Howard (New York State Department of Education), 1907 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rogers, Sara B., 1906 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rogers, Saul E. (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rogers, Theodore, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rogers, W.A., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rolt-Wheeler, Francis (Current Literature Publishing), 1911 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Romero, Bolivar S., 1931 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Roorback, E. (The Craftsman), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rosenbaum, Robert, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Roush, G.A. (Mineral Industry journal), 1914, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rowe, Leo S. (American Academy of Political and Social Science), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Informs Kunz of his enrollment in the academy.
- Rowan, Edward B., 1931 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rowland, Mirwin Dwight, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rudler, F.W., 1892 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rupp, George P. (Girard College), 1892-1897 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ruppel (Gutenberg Museum at Mainz), 1930 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Russ, Edward, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rustomjee, J. Cama-Rustom, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ryerson, Martin A., 1903 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Misc. R, 1903, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Sabin, Charles H. (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sabine, Lillian, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sackett, [?], 1912 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sackett, Alan [or Clara?], undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sackett, Elizabeth Titus, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Safford, May, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  The item is a postcard with a picture of Mr. & Mrs. Bok's house in Mountain Lake.
- Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Saltus, J. Sanford, 1900-1921 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Includes several letters from Saltus on various topics, including proposals to acquire or strike medals, apparently in connection with the Numismatics Society.
- Sandberg, Fred W., 1902 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sammis, Theodore (J.W. Bouton, dealer), 1887 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sargent, Irene, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sargent, Porter (publisher), 1922 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Saunders, William Lawrence, 1921-1925 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sawyer, F.L (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sayford, Irving S., 1925 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sayre, Francis Bowes (Williams College), 1914 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Schenck, Edwin S., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Scherer, James A. B. (Throop Polytechnic Institute), 1913 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schernikow, Ernest, 1904, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schling, Louise, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schling, Max, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schmal [Schmab?], J., 1893 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schofield, Sim, 1908, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Includes a poem "On Mi Retirement to 'The Nook,' Thornton-le-Fylde" (1917) by Schofield.
- Schroder, Catherine, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schuman, Jacob Gould (Cornell U), 1914-1920 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schwarz, Herbert F. (American Museum of Natural History), 1921-1922 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Schweinfurth, Charles Frederick, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Scott, John Winfield, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Scott, Walter (Union League), 1909, 1922, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Scribner, Arthur H. (Charles Scribner's Sons), 1916, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Seaman, Louis Livingston, 1920, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Seccombe, Mary F., 1929 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Secor, David Pell, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Secor, Florence Romola, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Seever, W.J. (Seever & Co, engravers), 1890 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Seinecke, Ferdinand (Deutscher Press Club), 1911 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Seitz, Mildred E. (Mrs. Don C.) (Daughters of the Revolution), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Selfridge, Lois Frances, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Seligman, Edwin R., 1920 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Sellig, W.L., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Seton, Ann, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Seton, May Thompson, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Settleton, Martin W., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shanahan, W.F. (Hotel Elysee), 1931 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shane, William, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shattuck, Mary, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shaw, Albert (American Monthly Review of Reviews), 1906-1913 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shelton, William Henry (Washington Headquarters Association), 1910 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Includes a letter written by Shelton to the New York Times about a New York Pageant
- Shepard, Charles U., 1907 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shepard, Finley Johnson (Mayor's Committee for the Entertainment of the U.S. Atlantic Fleet), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Sherwood, Alserda B., 1924 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Shipp, Thomas R. (Joint Committee on Conservation), 1909 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Short, Frank L. (Shakespeare Fellowship of America), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Sickels, David Banks, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Silskey, Edward (New York Public Library), 1894, 1909, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 7)